
export interface QuestionData {
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}



export const FOOTBALL_TRIVIA: QuestionData[] = [
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Manager of the Month award for August?",
    "answer": "Arne Slot"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Crystal Palace’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Selhurst Park"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these teams has played in every season of the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Everton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the first player to score a hat-trick as a substitute in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many clean sheets did Peter Schmeichel keep in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "128"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Fulham’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Craven Cottage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which active Premier League player has the most appearances in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "James Milner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has the record for the longest scoring streak in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Jamie Vardy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two teams are involved in the Tyne-Wear Derby?",
    "answer": "Sunderland, Newcastle United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the youngest player to have reach the 100 goal milestone in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Michael Owen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Villans”?",
    "answer": "Aston Villa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club plays its home matches at Anfield?",
    "answer": "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League titles does Manchester United have?",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Liverpool’s all-time leading goal scorer?",
    "answer": "Ian Rush"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Blues”?",
    "answer": "Chelsea"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League teams are competing in European competitions this season?",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Sunderland?",
    "answer": "Regis Le Bris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Burnley?",
    "answer": "Josh Cullen"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long is the record streak for a player scoring in consecutive Premier League games?",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many games does each team play in a Premier League season?",
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals and assist did Mohamed Salah achieve in the 2024/25 season?",
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for fewest points in a season while winning the Premier League?",
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which active Premier League player has scored the most goals in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League matches have been played on Christmas Eve?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Wolverhampton Wanderer’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Raul Jimenez"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Manchester United?",
    "answer": "Bruno Fernandes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the fastest goal in the Premier League as a substitute?",
    "answer": "Nicklas Bendtner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Cottagers”?",
    "answer": "Fulham"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Leeds United’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Mark Viduka"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals did Thierry Henry score for Arsenal in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "175"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club plays its home matches at American Express Stadium?",
    "answer": "Brighton & Hove Albion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Arsenal?",
    "answer": "Mikel Arteta"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Player of the Month award for October?",
    "answer": "Bryan Mbeumo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Aston Villa?",
    "answer": "John McGinn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Brighton & Hove Albion?",
    "answer": "Lewis Dunk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the youngest goalscorer in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "James Vaughan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most clean sheets kept by a goalkeeper in one Premier League season?",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the number of Premier League matches scheduled for Boxing Day this season?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the oldest manager to have managed in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Roy Hodgson"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many games did Arsene Wenger manage in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "828"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the inaugural winner of the Premier League when it was formed?",
    "answer": "Manchester United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most expensive Premier League transfer?",
    "answer": "Alexander Isak"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League titles does Arsenal have?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams from London compete in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most consecutive appearances in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Brad Friedel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Seagulls”?",
    "answer": "Brighton & Hove Albion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team won the Premier League title with the best defensive record in a season?",
    "answer": "Chelsea"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the last match of the 2025/26 Premier League festive fixture schedule?",
    "answer": "Manchester City vs Chelsea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which goalkeeper holds the record for most consecutive clean sheets in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Edwin van der Sar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Brentford’s all-time Premier League goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Yoane Wissa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the derby between Arsenal and Tottenham Hotspur called?",
    "answer": "North London Derby"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Sunderland’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Kevin Phillips"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Tottenham Hotspur?",
    "answer": "Cristian Romero"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Everton?",
    "answer": "Seamus Coleman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the fastest hat-trick in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Sadio Mane"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only goalkeeper to have won the Premier League Player of the Season award?",
    "answer": "Peter Schmeichel"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams have won the Premier League by going unbeaten in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the derby between Manchester United and Manchester City called?",
    "answer": "Manchester Derby"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Brentford’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Gtech Community Stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team plays their home matches at Villa Park?",
    "answer": "Aston Villa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Reds”?",
    "answer": "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Brighton & Hove Albion’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Danny Wellbeck"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Manchester City?",
    "answer": "Bernardo Silva"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club plays its home matches at St. James’ Park?",
    "answer": "Newcastle United"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the longest unbeaten home run in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Player of the Month award for September?",
    "answer": "Erling Haaland"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most goals scored by one player in a single Premier League season?",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Welsh clubs have competed in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Fulham?",
    "answer": "Marco Silva"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Tottenham Hotspur play their home games?",
    "answer": "Tottenham Hotspur stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the highest scoring midfielder in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Frank Lampard"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many seasons has Pep Guardiola been the manager of Manchester City (including this season)?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Premier League founded?",
    "answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many matches will each team play over the 2025/26 Premier League festive fixture?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Newcastle United?",
    "answer": "Eddie Howe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team holds the record for the most total goals scored in a single Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goalkeepers have scored a goal in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Nottingham Forest?",
    "answer": "Sean Dyche"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these teams won the Premier League undefeated?",
    "answer": "Arsenal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has the record for the most points in a single Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only player to have scored for seven different clubs in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Craig Bellamy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Arsenal’s unbeaten Premier League title-winning season known as?",
    "answer": "The Invincibles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for the most consecutive Premier League games played by a player?",
    "answer": "310"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Brentford?",
    "answer": "Nathan Collins"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long is the longest unbeaten run in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these matches has been played on Christmas Eve in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Wolverhampton Wanderers vs Chelsea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has played for the most Premier League teams?",
    "answer": "Marcus Bent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Including the current season, how many Premier League seasons have been played?",
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Crystal Palace?",
    "answer": "Marc Guehi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Leeds United?",
    "answer": "Ethan Ampadu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first goal of the 2025/26 Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Hugo Ekitike"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total appearances did Peter Schmeichel make in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "310"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for the most Premier League Golden Boot awards won by a player?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different teams have played in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the biggest title-winning margin in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "19 Points"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Chelsea’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Frank Lampard"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many clean sheets did Chelsea keep in their title winning 2004/05 season?",
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many games did Erling Haaland take to score 100 goals in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "111"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Tottenham Hotspur’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Harry Kane"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Aston Villa’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Ollie Watkins"
  },
  {
    "question": "How fast was the fastest goal scored by a substitute in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "6 seconds"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals did Chelsea concede in their title winning 2004/05 season?",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player holds the record for most hat-tricks in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Sergio Aguero"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Wolverhampton Wanderer’s nickname?",
    "answer": "Wolves"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Newcastle United’s nickname?",
    "answer": "The Magpies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is West Ham United’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Michail Antonio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Wolverhampton Wanderers?",
    "answer": "Toti Gomes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Newcastle United?",
    "answer": "Bruno Guimaraes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Brentford?",
    "answer": "Keith Andrews"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for most assists in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "162"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Nottingham Forest?",
    "answer": "Ryan Yates"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the longest serving manager in the Premier League right now?",
    "answer": "Pep Guardiola"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these teams has Scott Parker not managed in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Tottenham Hotspur"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Manchester City’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Etihad Stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League titles has Manchester City won?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Aston Villa?",
    "answer": "Unai Emery"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Everton’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Romelu Lukaku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for the most Premier League Golden Glove awards won by a goalkeeper?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Fulham?",
    "answer": "Tom Cairney"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Manchester United?",
    "answer": "Ruben Amorim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Gunners”?",
    "answer": "Arsenal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the oldest player to have played in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "John Burridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Player of the Month award for August?",
    "answer": "Jack Grealish"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for most consecutive Premier League wins by a team?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has won the most Premier League titles?",
    "answer": "Manchester United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these teams played in the first season of the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Aston Villa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Premier League team has the nickname “The Eagles”?",
    "answer": "Crystal Palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Premier League’s all-time goal scoring record?",
    "answer": "260"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these teams were promoted into the Premier League this season?",
    "answer": "Burnley"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League titles has Liverpool won?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many English managers have won the Premier League title?",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has managed the most Premier League teams?",
    "answer": "Sam Allardyce"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many matches are scheduled to be played during the 2025/26 Premier League festive fixture?",
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the longest-serving manager in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Arsene Wenger"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Manchester City’s 2017/18 title-winning season known as?",
    "answer": "Centurions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most consecutive Premier League title wins?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only defender to have won the Player of the Season award multiple times (2 or more)?",
    "answer": "Nemanja Vidic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Bournemouth’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Joshua King"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Premier League team plays at the London Stadium?",
    "answer": "West Ham United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Burnley?",
    "answer": "Scott Parker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only player to have scored five goals in a single half of a Premier League match?",
    "answer": "Jermain Defoe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Brighton & Hove Albion?",
    "answer": "Fabian Hurzeler"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who are the current defending champions of the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many players have won the Player of the Season award multiple times (2 or more)?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Sunderland’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Stadium of Light"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player holds the record for the quickest goal scored in Premier League history (7.69 seconds)?",
    "answer": "Shane Long"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Chelsea?",
    "answer": "Reece James"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Manchester City’s all-time top scorer?",
    "answer": "Sergio Aguero"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Liverpool?",
    "answer": "Virgil van Dijk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first hat-trick of the Premier League era?",
    "answer": "Eric Cantona"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Premier League’s all-time top scorer?",
    "answer": "Alan Shearer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Nottingham Forest play their home games?",
    "answer": "City Ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams are relegated from the Premier League each season?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Tottenham Hotspur’s nickname?",
    "answer": "The Lilywhites"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many players have scored 100 goals or more in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team won the Premier League four times in a row?",
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Leeds United?",
    "answer": "Daniel Farke"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Premier League team has the nickname “The Garibaldis”?",
    "answer": "Nottingham Forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Clarets”?",
    "answer": "Burnley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of West Ham United?",
    "answer": "Jarred Bowen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the top goalscorer in the Premier League last season?",
    "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Manchester United play their home games?",
    "answer": "Old Trafford"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most number of wins achieved by a team in a single Premier League season?",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most number of goals scored by a player in a single Premier League match?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Arsenal’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Thierry Henry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many games did it take for Erling Haaland to score three hat-tricks in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the nickname of Leeds United?",
    "answer": "The Whites"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Bournemouth?",
    "answer": "Andoni Iraola"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Premier League’s all-time clean sheet record?",
    "answer": "202"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for most Premier League assists in a season?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player currently playing in the Premier League has scored the most goals in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Crystal Palace’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Wilfried Zaha"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the oldest stadium in the Premier League this season?",
    "answer": "Stamford Bridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first match to kick off the 2025/26 Premier League festive fixtures?",
    "answer": "Chelsea vs Newcastle United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Arsenal?",
    "answer": "Martin Odegaard"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams compete in the Premier League each season?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the highest number of goals scored by a player in a single Premier League season?",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first goal in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Brian Diane"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the goalkeeper with the most assists in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Ederson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Fulham’s all-time leading Premier League goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Clint Dempsey"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for the most consecutive Premier League games played by an outfield player?",
    "answer": "164"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club plays its home games at Stamford Bridge?",
    "answer": "Chelsea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which stadium in the Premier League has the largest capacity",
    "answer": "Old Trafford"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team uses “You’ll Never Walk Alone” as a motto?",
    "answer": "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team holds the record for the largest Premier League title-winning margin?",
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Everton play their home games before moving to their new stadium?",
    "answer": "Goodison Park"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Hammers”?",
    "answer": "West Ham United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the youngest manager to have managed in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "Ryan Mason"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Everton?",
    "answer": "David Moyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the other goalkeeper besides Petr Cech to have won the most Premier League Golden Glove awards?",
    "answer": "Joe Hart"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Chelsea?",
    "answer": "Enzo Maresca"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most clean sheets in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Petr Cech"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the other player besides Mohamed Salah to have won the most Premier League Golden Boot awards?",
    "answer": "Thierry Henry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Leeds play their home games?",
    "answer": "Elland Road"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams competed during the first-ever Premier League season?",
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Premier League team plays at the Emirates Stadium?",
    "answer": "Arsenal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Nottingham Forest’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Chris Wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first hat-trick of the 2025/26 Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Jean-Philippe Mateta"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Toffees”?",
    "answer": "Everton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Burnley’s all-time Premier League top goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Chris Wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club is nicknamed “The Black Cats”?",
    "answer": "Sunderland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Crystal Palace?",
    "answer": "Oliver Glasner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Bournemouth?",
    "answer": "Adam Smith"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Manager of the Month award for September?",
    "answer": "Oliver Glasner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Premier League Manager of the Month award for October?",
    "answer": "Ruben Amorim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which goalkeeper has saved the most penalties?",
    "answer": "David James"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player has won the most Premier League titles?",
    "answer": "Ryan Giggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the longest consecutive scoring streak in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the manager that led Chelsea to the 2004/05 Premier League title?",
    "answer": "Jose Mourinho"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the first match of the 2025/26 Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Liverpool vs Bournemouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Bournemouth play their home games?",
    "answer": "Vitality Stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these matches will be the first Premier League match of 2026?",
    "answer": "Liverpool vs Leeds United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the title-winning goal for Manchester City against Queens Park Rangers in the 2011/12 Premier League season?",
    "answer": "Sergio Aguero"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club famously won the Premier League title on goal difference in 2011/12?",
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these matches will not be played during the 2025/26 Premier League festive fixture?",
    "answer": "Newcastle United vs Brentford"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of West Ham United?",
    "answer": "Nuno Espirito Santo"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League titles has Chelsea won?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Burnley play their home games?",
    "answer": "Turf Moor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player mode the most appearances in the Premier League for a single club?",
    "answer": "Ryan Giggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Newcastle United’s all-time leading Premier League goalscorer?",
    "answer": "Alan Shearer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Manchester United’s nickname?",
    "answer": "The Red Devils"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Wolverhampton Wanderer’s stadium?",
    "answer": "Molineux Stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals did Thierry Henry score for Arsenal in the 2003/04 Premier League season?",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these players have appeared in the most Premier League seasons?",
    "answer": "James Milner"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most assist by a goalkeeper?",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the captain of Sunderland?",
    "answer": "Granit Xhaka"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the all-time leading assist maker in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "Ryan Giggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Liverpool?",
    "answer": "Arne Slot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which manager has won the most Premier League titles?",
    "answer": "Sir Alex Ferguson"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bournemouth’s nickname?",
    "answer": "The Cherries"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many players have scored more than 200 goals in Premier League history?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams have never been relegated from the Premier League since its inception?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most number of goals scored by a team in a Premier League season?",
    "answer": "106"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total appearances did Alan Shearer make in the Premier League?",
    "answer": "441"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the oldest outfield player to score a Premier League goal?",
    "answer": "Teddy Sheringham"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the manager of Wolverhampton Wanderers?",
    "answer": "Rob Edwards"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Premier League teams have successfully completed and won the treble?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first Premier League season played with 20 teams?",
    "answer": "1995/96"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Brentford’s nickname?",
    "answer": "The Bees"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different teams have won the Premier League?",
    "answer": "7"
  }
];
